John Cohen collection, circa 1939-2019
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2. Sound recordings and moving images, ca. 1950-2010
  - Subseries 4. Recordings and film parts related to Cohen's films, 1972-1992
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA103; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Hyatt - Epirotic soc.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA104; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. New London - wedding, tape 1.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA105; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. New London - wedding, tape 2.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA106 through AFC 2011/059: PIA108; 3 sound cassettes.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA109; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Train FX cued up.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA110; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Dena's radio tape.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA111; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Duplicate cassette #1 - Delvinaki Festival.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA112; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Duplicate cassette #2 - Delvinaki Festival.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA113; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Duplicate cassette #3 - Delvinaki Festival.
    - Pericles in America, 1987, AFC 2011/059: PIA114; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Duplicate cassette #4 - Delvinaki Festival.
    - Pericles in America, 1987, AFC 2011/059: PIA115; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Duplicate cassette #6 - Kastani (August 15, 1987) - Peristeri (August 16, 1987).
    - Pericles in America, 1987, AFC 2011/059: PIA116; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Duplicate cassette #7 - Peristeri (August 16, 1987).
    - Post Industrial Fiddle, ca. 1982, AFC 2011/059: PIF01 through AFC 2011/059: PIF16; 16 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Post Industrial Fiddle, exploring the life of a pulp mill worker and fiddle player in rural Maine.
    - Peruvian Weaving: A Continuous Warp, ca. 1982, AFC 2011/059: PWCW01 through AFC 2011/059: PWCW05; 5 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Peruvian Weaving: A Continuous Warp, about warp pattern weaving in Peru, an ancient Andean Indian tradition.
    - Q'eros: The Shape of Survival, ca. 1979, AFC 2011/059: QSS05 through AFC 2011/059: QSS58; 54 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Field recordings relating to the film, Q'eros: The Shape of Survival, a depiction of the way of life of the Q'eros Indians of Peru.
    - Sara and Maybelle, ca. 1981, AFC 2011/059: MV0021 through AFC 2011/059: MV0032; 12 16-millimeter color film
      Film footage of Sara and Maybelle Carter.
  - Subseries 5. Sound recordings and moving image materials from 2020 accrual, 1948-2010, undated
    Sound recordings and moving image material from 2020 accrual that do not fit into the topical subseries below, as well as paper documentation from sound recording and moving image containers and selected original sleeves from Huayno disc collection. The films are awaiting conservation treatment and further processing.
    - Documentation from sound recording containers, 1/2, 1950-2010, 1 folder (Box-folder 75/1)
    - Documentation from sound recording containers, 2/2, 1950-2010, 1 folder (Box-folder 75/2)
    - Huayno disc sleeves, ca. 1960-1990, 1 box (Box 82)
    - Huayno disc sleeves, ca. 1960-1990, 1 box (Box 83)
    - Documentation from film containers, 1/3, ca. 1948-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 75/3)
    - Documentation from film containers, 2/3, ca. 1948-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 75/4)
    - Documentation from film containers, 3/3, ca. 1948-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 75/5)
    - Documentation related to afc2011059_dc057: Talking Feet: Solo Southern Dance: Flatfoot, Buck, and Tap, ca. 1990-1992, 1 folder (Box-folder 75/6)
    - Unidentified recording, undated, 1 sound cassette (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR665)
    - Irish folk music, undated, 1 sound cassette (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR667)
    - Goose Mother, undated, 1 sound cassette (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR668)
    - Time with Murray, interview, undated, 1 sound cassette (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR676)
    - 1950 1st, 1950, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0131)
    - 1950 2nd, 1950, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0132)
    - 1950 3rd, 1950, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0133)
    - Outs/Mary Jane Talks Quilts, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0141)
    - Ballet Dancer, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0142)
    - Sweets Mill, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0143)
    - Cada[?] Flag, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0144)
    - Unidentified film reel #1, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0145)
    - Unidentified film reel #2, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0146)
    - Unidentified film reel #3, undated, 1 film reel, 16mm (Item-id AFC 2011/059: MV0147)
- Series 3. Still images, ca. 1954-2005
  Photographic prints and digitized contact sheets relating to folk musicians, Peru, the Beat scene in New York, and Cohen's other projects and phases of life.
  - Subseries 1. Photographic prints, ca. 1956-1983
    Photographic prints from various aspects of Cohen's life and career. Includes prints of the folk music scene in and around Greenwich Village, including musicians, concerts, jams, and folk festivals. Includes photographic prints related to Cohen's project, Past Present Peru. Materials document weaving and spinning traditions, as well as music, dancing, and other activities of communities in Peru. Descriptions are derived from Cohen's writing and labels.
    - Musicians: Still frames from Musical Holdouts (film), ca. 1976, 6 black-and-white prints: various sizes (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Musicians: High Atmosphere prints, ca. 1975, 41 black-and-white prints: 8x10 in. (Box-folder 27/2-3)
      Landers, Wade Ward, etc. - miscellaneous Southern Trip. 1961 with Mike Seeger. Prints related to the 1975 compilation album released by Rounder Records.
    - Musicians: Bluegrass, ca. 1960s, 62 black-and-white prints: various sizes (Box-folder 27/4-6)
      Includes Cohen's photographs of the Stanley Brothers, Bill Monroe, Earl Scruggs, the Lilly Brothers, the Stoney Mountain Boys (Earle Taylor), and the Country Gentlemen.
    - Musicians: New Lost City Ramblers photographs, ca. 1957-1965, 48 black-and-white prints; 1 contact sheet; 1 color print (Box-folder 41/1)
      Separated from series 1. box 8, folder 86. Includes duplicate photographic prints.
    - Musicians: Negatives - NLCR and Strachwitz, ca. 1957-1965, 121 negatives; 3 contact sheets; 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 41/2)
      Separated from series 1. box 12, folder 131. From writing on original folder: "NLCR [New Lost City Ramblers] photo and negs, Larry Siegel."
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Muddy Waters, 1959, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Sara & Maybelle Carter film stills, ca. 1981, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Eck Robertson, 1963-1965, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 27/9)
      Includes prints of Eck Robertson, and one with Robertson and Roscoe Holcomb from the 1965 Newport Folk Festival.
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Harry Smith at Chelsea Hotel, undated, 13 black-and-white prints: various sizes (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Important 78 record collectors & Pat Conte at his home, undated, 11 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Janie Hunter's kids, 1963-1965, 5 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/1)
      John's Island, South Carolina.
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Walter Pardon - Knapton Norwich England, ca. 1981-1982, 16 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/2)
      Photographic prints related to the film, Gypsies Sing Long Ballads.
    - Miscellaneous country parks, undated, 8 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Woody Guthrie, ca. 1961-1966, 21 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/4)
      Alternates, variants, and 4 photographs by Arthur Dubinsky.
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Doc Watson and [Clarence] Ashley, ca. 1961-1965, 33 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/5-6)
      Recording in New York, 1961 (Gaither Carlton, Tom Ashley, Doc Watson); 1st concert of FoTM [Friends of Old Time Music], [Clarence] Ashley, Fred Price, and Clint Howard, Galax 1963; Party near Doc Watson's home, Deep Gap, Carolina; University of Chicago, backstage, Ralph Rinzler and Eck Robertson, Newport Folk Festival, 1965.
    - Miscellaneous musicians: Elizabeth Cotten, 1960, 7 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/7)
      Washington, D.C.
    - Various musicians: Various, LOC prints, misc., ca. 1961 and undated, 5 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 30/6)
      Includes photographic prints of Hazel Dickens and Alice Gerrard, Eck Robertson, Wade Ward, and others.
    - Various musicians: Mostly non-John Cohen photographs, ca. 1980s, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 30/7)
      Includes photographic prints and photographs printed on paper from Pericles in America and Musical Holdouts, as well as of other musicians, such as Rayna Gellert. Photographers include Dena Schultzer and Martin Koenig.
    - Various musicians: Musicians - various & miscellaneous, ca. 1957-1967, 25 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/1)
      Includes photographic prints of Elizabeth Cotten, Mike Seeger, Alice Gerrard, Roscoe Holcomb, Woody Guthrie, Alan Lomax, Muddy Waters, and others. Includes a print from Izzy Young's Folklore Center, circa 1957.
    - Various musicians: Related - mostly non-John Cohen photos, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 38/2)
      Photographic print of Rufus Crisp, related to Pericles in America film.
    - Mike Seeger wedding, Folksong '59: Mike Seeger wedding party, and other photographs of musicians, ca. 1957-1965, 46 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 33/4-5)
      University of Chicago Folk Festival, Newport Folk Festival, and Greenwich Village photographs. Includes photographs from Izzy Young's Folklore Center. Includes photographs of Ralph Rinzler and the Greenbriar Boys, Memphis Slim, Bukka White, Clarence White, John Jackson, Bessie Jones, Dock Boggs, Dock Watson, Hobart Smith, Skiffle Band, Joan Baez, Janis Ian, Alice Gerrard, Hazel Dickens, Bruce Molsky, and others.
    - Mike Seeger wedding, Folksong '59: Alan Lomax, Pete Seeger, Muddy Waters, et al., ca. 1959 and undated, 23 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 33/6-7)
      Photographs of rehearsals for Folksong '59 in New York City. Includes photographs of Alan Lomax, Pete Seeger, Mike Seeger, Ralph Rinzler, Muddy Waters, Jimmy Driftwood, Gospel Singers, and Toshi Seeger.
    - Roscoe Holcomb portraits, etc., ca. 1959-1965, 29 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 33/8-9)
      Includes photographs of Roscoe Holcomb, Bill Monroe, Pete Seeger, and unidentified musicians.
    - German tour 1966: German/Europe tour 1966, ca. 1966, 29 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/1-2)
      Photographs from the Festival of American Folk & Country Music in Germany and accompanying European tour. Includes photographs of Ralph and Carter Stanley, Roscoe Holcomb, Cousin Emmy, Mike Seeger, Adam and Cyp Landreneou
    - Dillard Chandler & Ballad Singers & landscapes, ca. 1963-1965, 21 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/3)
      "Old ballad singers from film, The End of An Old Song in Sodom, North Carolina. Includes photographs of Dillard Chandler, Lee Wallin, Cass Wallin, and Berzilla Wallin.
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: Steidle Book Prints, undated, 7 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/8)
      Inventoried by ACMS for appraisal.
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: Cuzco, street photography, ca. 1975, 18 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/9)
      Cuzco, the center of the Inca Empire.
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: White Man's World, 1956, 9 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/10)
      Includes "Dance of the Old Men." Prints are also in Mountain Music of Peru.
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: Inca stones/Indian lives, ca. 1957, 12 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/11)
      Includes prints of stone structures in Peru, as well as people from the Q'eros community.
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: Andeans, ca. 1977, 10 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 28/12)
      Includes prints of the Q'eros community on their land.
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: Oh God, 1956, 18 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Past Present Peru, part 1: Island of Prayers, 1956, 12 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/2)
      From collector documentation: "Taquili, 1956, drought. They prayed for rain in their church and then at an ancient shrine."
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Trucking across the Andes, ca. 1956-1957, 26 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/3-4)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Qeros: The far side of the mountains, ca. 1956-1957, 22 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Qeros: Thanking the llamas for carrying the corn up from the jungle, ca. 1956-1957, 19 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: "Dispacho" - a message to the gods, ca. 1956-1957, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Potato planters, ca. 1956-1957, 10 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Hydro-electricity, ca. 1956-1957, 8 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Living landscapes/standing stones, ca. 1956-1957, 18 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Peru weaving from Past Present Peru, ca. 1956-1957, 54 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 30/1-3)
      Music and Weaving. Most images from 1956-1957.
    - Past Present Peru, part 2: Peru music for Past Present Peru, ca. 1956-1957, 21 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 30/4-5)
    - Past Present Peru part 3: 11x14 good prints for Peru photo book, ca. 1956-1977, 15 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Inca Monuments: Taquili, ca. 1958, 33 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 30/8-9)
    - Inca Monuments: Taquili, ca. 1956, 38 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 39/1-2)
    - Inca Monuments: Inca monuments, etc., ca. 1956-1957, 13 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 30/10)
    - Inca Monuments: Inca monuments, etc., ca. 1956-1957, 7 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Cohen, Q'eros & Neighbors: Q'eros neighbors, ca. 1956-1957, 26 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Cohen, Q'eros & Neighbors: Q'eros neighbors, ca. 1956-1957, undated, 16 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Cohen, Q'eros & Neighbors: Q'eros, 1950s, 1977-1983, 98 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/5-8)
    - Cohen, Q'eros & Neighbors: Q'eros, 1950s, 1977-1983, 43 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 40/2-3)
    - ADDL weaving prints: Spinning wool, ca. 1956-1957, 33 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/2-3)
      Spinning wool; close up of hands photographs.
    - ADDL weaving prints: Spinning cotton, ca. 1956-1957, 15 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/4)
      Spinning cotton - north coast (sechura, rivra, monsefo).
    - ADDL weaving prints: Setting up warps, ca. 1956-1957, 24 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/5-6)
    - ADDL weaving prints: Opening sheds with heddles & fingers, ca. 1956-1957, 31 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/7-8)
    - ADDL weaving prints: Pick-ups in warp, ca. 1956-1957, 17 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/9)
      Pick out designs (palley) - termination areas.
    - ADDL weaving prints: "Huatay" poncho, ca. 1956-1957, 20 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 31/10)
      At (Catcca) (Cuzco dept) - tie dye.
    - ADDL weaving prints: Ikat (tie dying) at San Miguel de Cajamarca, ca. 1956-1957, 48 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/1-2)
    - ADDL weaving prints: Miscellaneous material, ca. 1956-1957, 29 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/3-4)
      Foot heddles, blessing warp, teaching, wide loom (at Tupe-Yauos), Bayeta on 4 stake loom (Qeros).
    - Peru: Miscellaneous vintage scraps, 1956-1957, 31 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/5-6)
      Photographic prints of music making, dancing, and other activities from Peru.
    - Peru: Miscellaneous Peru 1, ca. 1956-1957, 58 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/7-9)
    - Peru: Miscellaneous Peru 2, ca. 1956-1957, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Peru: Past Present Peru photos not in the book, ca. 1956-1957, 18 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Peru: Q'eros, 2005, miscellaneous, undated, 17 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 32/12)
      Likely photographs from the 1950s, but reprinted in 2005.
    - Peru: Q'eros, 2005, miscellaneous, undated, 36 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 33/1-2)
    - Peru: Qeros llama corral 2005, undated, 21 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 33/3-4)
    - Mestizo - town, coast, Lima: Mestizo life, ca. 1956-1964, 24 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/4)
      Includes "kids dancing, Huancualica (cover of Folkways album, vol. 2)."
    - 17 Mag[azine], Sr. Morusky: Sr. Morusky (?), Robert Frank's contact, undated, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/1)
      "Lived in very old Lima house which became a famous restaurant - Strikers in Lima street."
    - 17 Mag[azine], Sr. Morusky: Wealthy teenage girl in Lima for "17" magazine, ca. 1957, 56 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/2-4)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: Lima girl, "17," ca. 1957, 4 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: North Coast, ca. 1957, 10 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: Church, 1956-1957, 11 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: Festival, ca. 1957, undated, 6 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: Music, ca. 1956-1964, undated, 25 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: Lima, ca. 1982, undated, 9 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: [Cuzco life], undated, 9 black-and-white prints, 11x14 in. (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Mestizo - Town, Coast, Lima: Mestizo life, ca. 1957, undated, 19 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Subseries 2. There Is No Eye exhibit photographic prints, ca. 1950-1999
    Gelatin silver photographic prints from, There Is No Eye, an exhibition of Cohen's photographs organized by The Photographic Resource Center in Boston.
    - Tenth Street, New York City, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Macchu Tussec Dancers, Juli, Peru, 1957, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Harlem, New York City, 1954, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Robert Frank and Larry Rivers, New York City, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Chucuito, Peru, 1964, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Chucuito, Peru, 1964, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Woody Guthrie, Cooper Union, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Roscoe Holcomb, Daisy, Kentucky, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/8)
    - Red Grooms "The Burning Building," 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/9)
    - Jack Kerouac listening to himself on the radio, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/10)
    - Roscoe Holcomb's hands, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/11)
    - Doc Watson and Gaither Carlton, first New York trip, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Reverend Gary Davis, New York City, 1954, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Tin Can Banjo, East Kentucky, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/14)
    - Robert Frank and Jack Kerouac on set of "Pull My Daisy," 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/15)
    - Sonya and Penny, Maine, 1974, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Roscoe Holcomb, 1964, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/17)
    - George Davis, The Singing Miner, Lothair, Kentucky, 1968, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/18)
    - Bill Monroe and his Blue Grass Boys, Hazard, Kentucky, 1962, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/19)
    - Leatherwood, Kentucky, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/20)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Sams, Combs, Kentucky, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/21)
    - Holiness Curch Service in a House, Daisy, Kentucky, 1962, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/22)
    - Sign, Hazard, Kentucky, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/23)
    - Perry County, Kentucky, 1959, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/24)
    - The Goat Man, North Carolina, 1967, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/25)
    - Lloyd Chandler, Sodom, North Carolina, 1965, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/26)
    - Dillard Chandler, Ballad Singer, Sodom, North Carolina, 1967, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/27)
    - Grandma Pearly Davis, Roaring River, North Carolina, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/28)
    - Pearly Davis' Home, Roaring River, North Carolina, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/29)
    - North Georgia, 1967, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 42/30)
    - Roscoe Holcomb, 1964, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/31)
    - The Stanley Brothers, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/32)
    - Charlie Higgins at Union Grove Fiddlers' Convention, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/33)
    - Old Fiddlers' Contest, Galax, Virginia, 1962, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/34)
    - Wade Ward and Charlie Higgins, Galax, Virginia, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/35)
    - Parking Lot Audience, Galax, Virginia, 1962, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/36)
    - Sidna Myers, Hillsville, Virginia, 1965, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/37)
    - Flatt and Scruggs, New River Rance, Maryland, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/38)
    - Backstage, Sunset Park, Maryland, 1961, 1 gelatin silver print (Box-folder 43/39)